<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andi Palo personal website</title>
    <link>https://andipalo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andi Palo personal website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 15:39:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andipalo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin: Binding Java Libraries to C#</title>
      <link>https://andipalo.com/posts/xamarin-bindings-java-seesharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 15:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andipalo.com/posts/xamarin-bindings-java-seesharp/</guid>
      <description>It has been exactly one year that I have been involved mobile application development with Xamarin and I would like to share an important experience that I have gained in this period. Xamarin is a powerful framework for cross-platform mobile application development which uses a modern and powerful language like C# but in the same time it offers access to the native Platform APIs and User Interface controls.
Another key aspect of Xamarin Framework is the ability to use native libraries (native is a relative term and in the Xamarin world it means developed in Java or Obj-C/Swift).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Codility &amp; Intercom</title>
      <link>https://andipalo.com/posts/codility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 19:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andipalo.com/posts/codility/</guid>
      <description>Last months have been trying to seek a career change. Among different job interviews and screenings I got to know also Intercom. It left an awesome and bitter experience. I did manage to go to the on-site interview but I did not get an offer (sigh)… but that story would belong to another post.

I spent three days in Dublin and had a chance to make a second visit to the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DB Amalgamation</title>
      <link>https://andipalo.com/posts/db-amalgamation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 10:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andipalo.com/posts/db-amalgamation/</guid>
      <description>I have always wanted to keep a blog but have always failed to create one, because of the lack of creativity and storytelling (as you will find out on this post). But in the recent two weeks I had an interesting work experience (and also funny) that I would like to share.
It begins with the necessity of one my managers to invite me for a two week period in the Italy office of the company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
